Guide to the American political campaigns miscellany, 1868-2016
American political campaigns miscellany
- Series IV. Broadsides
  - Democrats! Elect McCall Lt. Governor, ca. 1982; 6477.BR0100; Items: 1 (Box 18)
  - Municipal Socialist Platform (City of Ithaca), n/a; 6477.BR0101; Items: 1 (Box 1)
    Candidate: Scheltz, Mathias G.
    Party: Socialist
  - Campaign Letter (Forth Ward, Ithaca, Alderman & Supervisor), 1915; 6477.BR0102; Items: 2 (Box 1)
    Candidate: Merritt, Ernest
    Election: 1915
  - Forward With Stevenson (Sticker), 1952;1956; 6477.BR0103; Items: 1 (Box 1)
  - Sink Dewey!!, ca. 1952; 6477.BR0104; Items: 1 (Box 1)
    Candidate: Taft, Robert A.
  - Don't Be Fooled!, ca. 1952; 6477.BR0105; Items: 1 (Box 1)
  - Roosevelt's Supreme Council: A Non-Partisan Exposure..., 1936; 6477.BR0106; Items: 1 (Box 2)
    Election: 1936
  - Texans For Goldwater (Bumper Sticker), ca. 1964; 6477.BR0107; Items: 1 (Box 2)
  - Seeds Of Treason, 1964; 6477.BR0108; Items: 1 (Box 1)
  - The Who-Done-It of The Year (Radio Station W D I X Orangeburg S.C...), 1964; 6477.BR0109; Items: 1 (Box 1)
  - Letter From Hamilton Fish Challenging Charles E. Dusenberry To Debate, 1952; 6477.BR0110; Items: 1 (Box 1)
  - GOParty 1964 (Round red white & blue cardboart tag), 1964; 6477.BR0111; Items: 1 (Box 2)
  - Goldwater Miller Bumper Sticker (Orange & Black), 1964; 6477.BR0112; Items: 1 (Box 2)
  - Goldwater Miller 64 Bumper Sticker (Yellow on Red with White Arrow), 1964; 6477.BR0113; Items: 1 (Box 2)
  - Goldwater Miller Bumper Sticker (Blaze Orange & Black), 1964; 6477.BR0114; Items: 2 (Box 2)
  - Robison Is My Congressman Bumper Sticker (Black on Orange), 1964; 6477.BR0115; Items: 1 (Box 2)
  - Cook For Assembly Bumper Sticker (Orange on Dark Blue), 1964; 6477.BR0116; Items: 2 (Box 2)
  - LBJ USA Sticker (Shield- shaped), 1964; 6477.BR0117; Items: 1 (Box 2)
  - LBJ / USA Bumper Stickers, 1964; 6477.BR0118; Items: 2 (Box 2)
  - Johnson Humphrey For The USA Bumper Sticker (White on Red), 1964; 6477.BR0119; Items: 1 (Box 2)
  - Johnson Humphrey For The USA Bumper Sticker (White on Blue), 1964; 6477.BR0120; Items: 1 (Box 2)
  - Kennedy For United States Senator Bumper Stickers, 1964; 6477.BR0121; Items: 2 (Box 2)
    Candidate: Kennedy, Robert F.
  - New York Deserves The Best - Robert F. Kennedy...For U.S. Senator, 1964; 6477.BR0122; Items: 1 (Box 2)
  - Robert Kennedy Talks Abour The Issues..., 1964; 6477.BR0123; Items: 1 (Box 2)
  - Kennedy's Role As Attorney General, 1964; 6477.BR0124; Items: 1 (Box 2)
  - "To Preserve Freedom is The Highest Duty..."Robert F. Kennedy, 1964; 6477.BR0125; Items: 1 (Box 2)
  - Lighting His Own Way Robert Francis Kennedy, 1964; 6477.BR0126; Items: 1 (Box 17)
  - Keating's Voting Record...Elect Johnson-Humphrey-Kennedy, 1964; 6477.BR0127; Items: 1 (Box 2)
  - John L. Joy For U.S. Congress, 1964; 6477.BR0128; Items: 1 (Box 2)
    Candidate: Joy, John L.
  - No Vacancy' In N.Y., 1964; 6477.BR0129; Items: 1 (Box 2)
  - New York Explained, 1964; 6477.BR0130; Items: 1 (Box 2)
  - The Voters' Choice, 1964; 6477.BR0131; Items: 2 (Box 2)
  - In The G.O.P. Corner Kenneth Barnard Keating, 1964; 6477.BR0132; Items: 2 (Box 2)
  - Yes...We'll Baby-Sit For You...Get Out the Vote [Picture of Elephant], ca. 1964; 6477.BR0133; Items: 2 (Box 2)
  - Why Not Victory In New York?, 1964; 6477.BR0134; Items: 1 (Box 2)
  - Republican Calendar Of Political Programs TV And Radio, 1964; 6477.BR0135; Items: 1 (Box 2)
  - Exploding The No. 1 Campaign Myth, 1964; 6477.BR0135; Items: 1 (Box 2)
  - Why Do The Fat Cats The "Labor" Bosses Want Johnson?, 1964; 6477.BR0136; Items: 2 (Box 2)
  - Truth-Freedom-Charity What Will You Tell Your Children?, ca. 1964; 6477.BR0137; Items: 2 (Box 2)
  - Mr. President, Just Where Are We Headed?, 1964; 6477.BR0138; Items: 1 (Box 17)
  - Memorial Room 1:15 Congressman Robison, ca. 1964; 6477.BR0139; Items: 1 (Box 18)
  - Kennedy For President Bumper Sticker, ca. 1960; 6477.BR0140; Items: 1 (Box 2)
    Candidate: Kennedy, John F.
  - Nixon President Lodge Vice President Bumper Sticker, ca. 1960; 6477.BR0141; Items: 2 (Box 2)
  - Nixon Lodge Bumper Sticker, ca. 1960; 6477.BR0142; Items: 1 (Box 2)
  - Taber For Congress - Republican Bumper Sticker, ca. 1960; 6477.BR0143; Items: 1 (Box 2)
    Candidate: Taber, John
  - New York Needs An Upstate Governor! Vote Samuels...(Sticker), ca. 1970; 6477.BR0144; Items: 1 (Box 2)
    Candidate: Samuels, Howard J.
  - Attorney General Lefkowitz The People's Lawyer Bumper Sticker, ca. 1970; 6477.BR0145; Items: 1 (Box 2)
    Candidate: Lefkowitz, Louis J.
  - Buckley I've Joined the March For America Bumper Stickers, ca. 1970; 6477.BR0146; Items: 2 (Box 2)
  - Buckley (Small Stickers), ca. 1970; 6477.BR0147; Items: 2 (Box 2)
  - Re-Elect Robison Congress (Antenna Flag), ca. 1970; 6477.BR0148; Items: 2 (Box 18)
  - Re-Elect Javits (Stickers), 1968; 6477.BR0149; Items: 2 (Box 1)
    Candidate: Javits, Jacob K.
  - Javits Works For Me (Bumper Stickers), 1968; 6477.BR0150; Items: 2 (Box 2)
  - Senator Javits (Bumber Stickers), 1968; 6477.BR0151; Items: 2 (Box 2)
  - Humphrey Muskie (Bumper Stickers), 1968; 6477.BR0152; Items: 2 (Box 2)
  - McCarthy For President (Bumper Sticker), 1968; 6477.BR0153; Items: 1 (Box 2)
  - The War And The Cities (Reprinted from The New Republic, August 10...), 1968; 6477.BR0154; Items: 1 (Box 1)
  - Humphrey For President (Reprinted From The New York Times...), 1968; 6477.BR0155; Items: 2 (Box 2)
  - Rockefeller Pulls Ahead Of Humphrey...(Photocopies of Clippings), 1968; 6477.BR0156; Items: 1 (Box 2)
  - McCarthy On Civil Rights, ca. 1968; 6477.BR0157; Items: 1 (Box 1)
  - Eugene McCarthy Conscience In Politics, 1968; 6477.BR0158; Items: 1 (Box 17)
  - Farmers Need Gene McCarthy, ca. 1968; 6477.BR0159; Items: 1 (Box 1)
  - Who Picks Our Presidential Candidates?, ca. 1968; 6477.BR0160; Items: 1 (Box 2)
  - It's Now Or Never Vote for McCarthy Today, ca. 1968; 6477.BR0161; Items: 1 (Box 17)
  - Viet-Nam Veterans Speak Out, ca. 1968; 6477.BR0162; Items: 1 (Box 2)
  - McCarthy Scores Big At Demo Dinner Here, ca. 1968; 6477.BR0163; Items: 1 (Box 2)
  - Eugene McCarthy Looks To The Community..., ca. 1968; 6477.BR0164; Items: 1 (Box 1)
  - McCarthy's Farm Record, ca. 1968; 6477.BR0165; Items: 1 (Box 1)
  - It Is Now Or Never!!!, ca. 1968; 6477.BR0166; Items: 1 (Box 1)
  - McCarthy No Longer Alone, ca. 1968; 6477.BR0167; Items: 1 (Box 1)
  - Eugene McCarthy - Thoughts On The Presidency, ca. 1968; 6477.BR0168; Items: 1 (Box 1)
  - Eugene McCarthy On Foreign Policy (2 Copies: Same Text, Photos Differ), ca. 1968; 6477.BR0169; Items: 1 (Box 1)
  - McCarthy's "Complaints" (Reprinted from The New Republic), 1968; 6477.BR0170; Items: 1 (Box 1)
  - Leaders of "Texans For Kennedy" Announce McCarthy Support, ca. 1968; 6477.BR0171; Items: 1 (Box 1)
  - G.J. Sutton Endorses McCarthy In Texas, ca. 1968; 6477.BR0172; Items: 1 (Box 1)
  - Eugene McCarthy - Pro-Labor All The Way, ca. 1968; 6477.BR0173; Items: 1 (Box 1)
  - Eugene McCarthy Para Presidente, ca. 1968; 6477.BR0174; Items: 1 (Box 1)
  - Nixon Trailing HHH And McCarthy, 1968; 6477.BR0175; Items: 1 (Box 2)
  - State's Top Liberals Form Pro-McCarthy Group, 1968; 6477.BR0176; Items: 1 (Box 2)
  - Read What The New York Times Says About the Astonishing Mr. O'Dwyer, 1968; 6477.BR0177; Items: 1 (Box 1)
    Candidate: O'Dwyer, Paul
  - Photocopies Of Newspaper Clippings Concerning McCarthy, 1968; 6477.BR0178; Items: 6 (Box 2)
  - Johnson for President Bumper Sticker, ca. 1964; 6477.BR0179; Items: 1 (Box 2)
  - Republicans For Johnson Bumper Sticker, ca. 1964; 6477.BR0180; Items: 1 (Box 2)
  - Johnson Humphrey For The USA, ca. 1964; 6477.BR0181; Items: 1 (Box 2)
  - H H H Bumper Sticker, ca. 1968; 6477.BR0182; Items: 1 (Box 2)
  - HHH Humphrey Bumper Sticker, ca. 1968; 6477.BR0183; Items: 1 (Box 2)
  - Humphrey Bumper Sticker, ca. 1968; 6477.BR0184; Items: 1 (Box 2)
  - Humphrey/Muskie Bumper Sticker, ca. 1968; 6477.BR0185; Items: 1 (Box 17)
  - Nation Desperately Needs The Best: Hubert Humphrey, Edward Muskie, 1968; 6477.BR0186; Items: 1 (Box 2)
  - Humphrey For President (Handout From N.Y. State Labor Committee...), ca. 1968; 6477.BR0187; Items: 1 (Box 2)
  - Jobs Homes Schools Equality...HHH Tells It Like It Is, ca. 1968; 6477.BR0188; Items: 1 (Box 1)
  - Ford Dole Stickers (Round, Red White and Blue), ca. 1976; 6477.BR0189; Items: 2 (Box 1)
  - Ford Dole Bumper Sticker, ca. 1976; 6477.BR0190; Items: 1 (Box 1)
  - President Ford '76 Sticker, ca. 1976; 6477.BR0191; Items: 1 (Box 1)
  - Carter Mondale Bumper Stickers, ca. 1976; 6477.BR0192; Items: 2 (Box 2)
    Candidate: Carter, Jummy
  - Jimmy Carter President Bumper Stickers, ca. 1976; 6477.BR0193; Items: 2 (Box 2)
  - Moynihan Senator Bumper Sticker, ca. 1976; 6477.BR0194; Items: 1 (Box 2)
  - McHugh For Congress Bumper Stickers, ca. 1976; 6477.BR0195; Items: 2 (Box 2)
  - Bill Smith State Senator Bumper Sticker, ca. 1976; 6477.BR0196; Items: 1 (Box 17)
  - Carey A Fraud On The People Bumper Sticker, ca. 1976; 6477.BR0197; Items: 1 (Box 17)
    Candidate: Carey, Hugh W. (Anti)
  - Gary Lee Bumper Sticker, ca. 1976; 6477.BR0198; Items: 1 (Box 2)
  - Women's Campaigh Fund Fund-Raising Letter, ca. 1976; 6477.BR0199; Items: 1 (Box 1)
  - Jimmy Carter Presidential Campaign...Biography, 1974; 6477.BR0200; Items: 2 (Box 2)
  - Jobs...Not Welfare, 1976; 6477.BR0201; Items: 1 (Box 1)
  - On Tuesday We Can Get Our Government Back Again..., 1976; 6477.BR0202; Items: 1 (Box 1)
  - Jimmy Carter Walter Mondale Leaders For A Change, 1976; 6477.BR0203; Items: 1 (Box 1)
  - Dear Fourth Ward Voter..., 1976; 6477.BR0204; Items: 1 (Box 1)
  - Important Fourth Ward Issue: Historic District On East Hill, 1976; 6477.BR0205; Items: 1 (Box 1)
  - Compare The Platforms - Vote Democratic, 1976; 6477.BR0206; Items: 1 (Box 2)
  - People Who Cared Made America Great...Vote Ithaca New York 1976, 1976; 6477.BR0207; Items: 1 (Box 1)
  - Matt McHugh For Congress, ca. 1974; 6477.BR0208; Items: 1 (Box 1)
    Election: 1974
  - McHugh For Congress...Biography, ca. 1974; 6477.BR0209; Items: 1 (Box 1)
  - Rep. McHugh's Record On Key Votes, ca. 1976; 6477.BR0210; Items: 1 (Box 2)
  - Congressman Matt McHugh's Questionnaire Results, 1976; 6477.BR0211; Items: 2 (Box 2)
  - Congressman Matt McHugh (Policy statement sheets on five topics), ca. 1976; 6477.BR0212; Items: 5 (Box 1)
  - Udall...No Government Can Give You Dignity..., ca. 1976; 6477.BR0213; Items: 1 (Box 1)
    Candidate: Udall, Morris K.
  - Tompkins County Headquarters...(List of Udall Supporters), ca. 1976; 6477.BR0214; Items: 1 (Box 1)
  - A New Day Must Be Born (Anti-Nuclear Plea; Phil Berrigan and others), n/a; 6477.BR0215; Items: 1 (Box 1)
  - When Is Enough Enough? (Anti-Nuclear Plea; Phill Berrigan and others), n/a; 6477.BR0216; Items: 1 (Box 1)
  - Siegel State Senate Bumper Sticker, ca. 1980; 6477.BR0217; Items: 1 (Box 1)
    Candidate: Siegel, Ruth
  - The Time Is Now. Reagan & Bush Bumper Sticker, 1980;1984; 6477.BR0218; Items: 1 (Box 1)
    Election: 1980; 1984
  - Reagan-Bush '84 Bumper Sticker (Red, White and Blue), 1984; 6477.BR0219; Items: 2 (Box 1)
  - Reagan Bush '84 Bumper Sticker (White Letters On Blue), 1984; 6477.BR0220; Items: 1 (Box 1)
  - Reagan President Reagan Paper Banner, ca. 1984; 6477.BR0221; Items: 1 (Box 17)
  - The President Cares About Peace And About People, 1984; 6477.BR0222; Items: 2 (Box 1)
  - Wallace For Congress Bumper Sticker, ca. 1980; 6477.BR0223; Items: 1 (Box 1)
    Candidate: Wallace, Neil T.
  - Bill Smith State Senator Bumper Sticker, ca. 1980; 6477.BR0224; Items: 1 (Box 2)
    Candidate: Smith, William
  - Re-Elect Bob Howard Sheriff, ca. 1980; 6477.BR0225; Items: 1 (Box 2)
    Candidate: Howard, Robert L.
  - Stop ERA Sticker, n/a; 6477.BR0226; Items: 1 (Box 1)
  - By The Electoral Numbers...Reagan Well Ahead (Photocopy), 1980; 6477.BR0227; Items: 1 (Box 1)
  - Reagan On Israeli Security (Photocopy), 1980; 6477.BR0228; Items: 1 (Box 1)
  - Advertisement and Order Form For Reagan Independent Voter Kit, 1980; 6477.BR0229; Items: 1 (Box 1)
  - This Is A Great Country..., 1980; 6477.BR0230; Items: 1 (Box 1)
  - The Time Is Now, For Strong Leadership, 1980; 6477.BR0231; Items: 2 (Box 1)
  - Reagan & Bush For Young America the Time Is Now!, 1980; 6477.BR0232; Items: 2 (Box 1)
  - Reagan-Bush '84 Bumper Sticker (Red White & Blue. Differs fromBR0219), 1984; 6477.BR0233; Items: 1 (Box 2)
  - President Reagan Bringing America Back, 1984; 6477.BR0234; Items: 1 (Box 2)
  - Mondale Ferraro Bumper Sticker (Red White & Blue), 1984; 6477.BR0235; Items: 2 (Box 1)
    Candidate: Mondale, Walter F.
  - Mondale Ferraro Now Bumper Sticker (Green & White), 1984; 6477.BR0236; Items: 1 (Box 1)
  - Mondale Ferraro Round Sticker, 1984; 6477.BR0237; Items: 1 (Box 1)
  - Mondale Ferraro For America Round Stickers, 1984; 6477.BR0238; Items: 2 (Box 1)
  - McHugh for Congress Bumper Sticker (White on Very Dark Blue), 1984; 6477.BR0239; Items: 1 (Box 1)
  - Stan Lundine Bumper Sticker, ca. 1978; 1980; 1982; 1984; 6477.BR0240; Items: 1 (Box 1)
    Candidate: Lundine, Stanley
    Election: 1978; 1980; 1982; 1984
  - Jim Ball Congress '84 Bumper Sticker, 1984; 6477.BR0241; Items: 1 (Box 1)
    Candidate: Ball, James J.
  - "One Country One Flag One Language" Sticker, n/a; 6477.BR0242; Items: 1 (Box 1)
  - Republican Control Of the Senate Means Majority Leader Bob Dole..., ca. 1984; 6477.BR0243; Items: 1 (Box 1)
    Candidate: Dole, Robert
  - Ronald Reagan Has Never Supported Any Nuclear Arms Control..., ca. 1984; 6477.BR0244; Items: 1 (Box 1)
    Candidate: Reagan, Ronald (Anti)
  - It's Time To Choose, ca. 1984; 6477.BR0245; Items: 2 (Box 1)
  - The Freeze And The '84 Election (Upstate New York Freeze Voter), 1984; 6477.BR0246; Items: 1 (Box 2)
  - The Freeze And The '84 Election (Tompkins County...Freeze Campaign), 1984; 6477.BR0247; Items: 1 (Box 2)
  - Freeze Delegate Survey 28th C.D., ca. 1984; 6477.BR0248; Items: 1 (Box 1)
  - A Vote for Walter Mondale Is A Vote For:, 1984; 6477.BR0249; Items: 1 (Box 1)
  - Congressman Matt McHugh News, 1982; 6477.BR0250; Items: 4 (Box 2)
  - Benefits From The Excise Law...Tompkins County..., ca. 1904; 6477.BR0251; Items: 1 (Mapcase-folder X-24)
    Candidate: Higgins
    Election: 1904
  - State Tax Tompkins County...Saved To Taxpayers..., ca. 1904; 6477.BR0252; Items: 1 (Mapcase-folder X-24)
  - Vote No...For Canals...Broome County..., ca. 1904; 6477.BR0253; Items: 1 (Mapcase-folder X-24)
  - What It Will Cost Steuben County...Barge Canal..., ca. 1904; 6477.BR0254; Items: 1 (Mapcase-folder X-24)
  - Jay Gould's Conclusion, 1890; 6477.BR0255; Items: 1 (Mapcase-folder X-24)
  - Tax-Ridden Agriculture (L.L. Polk...National Farmers' Alliance...), 1890; 6477.BR0256; Items: 1 (Mapcase-folder X-24)
  - Why Don't the Foreigner Pay The Tax?, 1892; 6477.BR0257; Items: 1 (Mapcase-folder X-24)
  - Protection's "Home Market", 1890; 6477.BR0258; Items: 1 (Mapcase-folder X-24)
  - Iron Manufacture Needs No Protection, 1892; 6477.BR0259; Items: 1 (Mapcase-folder X-24)
  - The Agricultural Interest, 1879; 6477.BR0260; Items: 1 (Mapcase-folder X-24)
  - In The Table Which I Have Now Before Me...(Senator John Sherman), 1883; 6477.BR0261; Items: 1 (Mapcase-folder X-24)
  - Every Advance Towards A Free Exchange...(Senator John Sherman), 1868; 6477.BR0262; Items: 1 (Mapcase-folder X-24)
  - But What Is The Meaning Of Protection? (Daniel O'Connell), 1843; 6477.BR0263; Items: 1 (Mapcase-folder X-24)
  - The Manufacturer's Club Of Philadelphia..., n/a; 6477.BR0264; Items: 1
  - The Below, Copies Of Which The American Protectionists..., n/a; 6477.BR0265; Items: 1 (Mapcase-folder X-24)
  - McKinley's Fraud On Labor!, ca. 1890; 6477.BR0266; Items: 1 (Mapcase-folder X-24)
  - The Democrats Have Increased Taxes In Tompkins County, 1891; 6477.BR0267; Items: 1 (Mapcase-folder X-24)
  - Goodbye Pataki / Adios Pataki, 2002; 6477.BR0268; Items: 1 (Box 17)
    Candidate: McCall, H. Carl
    Election: 2002
  - McCall Governor, 2002; 6477.BR0269; Items: 1 (Box 17)
  - Elect Perot President (bumper stickers), 1992 or 1996; 6477.BR0270; Items: 2 (Box 23)
    Candidate: Perot, Ross
    Election: 1992 or 1996
    Party: Independent
  - Perot 92 (bumper sticker), 1992; 6477.BR0271; Items: 1 (Box 23)
    Election: 1992
  - I'm a Watch Dog"/Perot*IWSA [Illinois Workplace Skills Assessment] (bumper sticker), 1992 or 1996; 6477.BR0272; Items: 1 (Box 23)
  - Udall for President (bumper sticker), 1976; 6477.BR0273; Items: 1 (Box 23)
    Candidate: Udall, Morris
  - For America: Mondale/Ferraro (bumper sticker), 1984; 6477.BR0274; Items: 1 (Box 23)
    Candidate: Mondale, Walter and Geraldine Ferraro
  - Republican National Convention, Madison Square Garden, August 30th-September 2nd, New York City 2004 (broadside), 2004; 6477.BR0275; Items: 1 (Box 18)
  - Ross Perot for President, 1-800-283-ROSS (broadside), 1992 or 1996; 6477.BR0276; Items: 1 (Box 18)
  - Perot '92 (broadside), 1992; 6477.BR0277; Items: 1 (Box 18)
  - Kerry Edwards/A STRONGER AMERICA/JOHNKERRY.COM (bumper sticker), 2004; 6477.BR0278; Items: 1 (Box 23)
    Candidate: Kerry, John and John Edwards
  - Lynn Martin for US Senate bumper sticker, 6477.BR0279; Items: 1 (Box 26)
    Candidate: Martin, Lynn
  - Simon for President Bumper Sticker, 6477.BR0280; Items: 1 (Box 26)
    Candidate: Simon, Paul
  - Mario Cuomo bumper sticker, 6477.BR0281; Items: 1 (Box 26)
    Candidate: Cuomo, Mario
  - Mike Dukakis for President, 6477.BR0282; Items: 6 (Box 26)
    Candidate: Dukakis, Mike
  - Bob McMillan for US Senate bumper sticker, 6477.BR0283; Items: 1 (Box 26)
    Candidate:
  - Dole for President bumper sticker, 6477.BR0284; Items: 1 (Box 26)
    Candidate: Dole, Bob
  - George Bush for President bumper sticker, 6477.BR285; Items: 2 (Box 26)
    Candidate: Bush, George
  - New Yorkers for Jesse Jackson bumper sticker, 6477.BR0286; Items: 1 (Box 26)
    Candidate: Jackson, Jesse
  - Ronald Lauder for Mayor bumper sticker, 6477.BR0287; Items: 1 (Box 26)
    Candidate: Lauder, Ronald
  - Giuliani for Mayor bumper sticker, 6477.BR0288; Items: 1 (Box 26)
  - Mondale/Ferraro bumper sticker, 6477.BR0289; Items: 1 (Box 26)
  - Al Gore for President, 1988; 6477.BR0290; Items: 1 (Box 26)
    Candidate: Gore, Al
  - Vote Republican bumper sticker, 6477.BR0291; Items: 1 (Box 26)
  - Ed Koch for Mayor bumper sticker, 6477.BR0292; Items: 1 (Box 26)
    Candidate: Koch, Ed
  - Bush/Quayle bumper sticker, 1988; 6477.BR0293; Items: 1 (Box 26)
    Candidate: Bush/Quayle
    Election:1988
  - Kutun stickers, 6477.BR0294; Items: 1 (Box 26)
  - Bill Green for Congress sticker, 6477.BR0295; Items: 1 (Box 26)
    Candidate: Green, Bill
  - Dinkins sticker, 6477.BR0296; Items: 2 (Box 26)
    Candidate: Dinkins, David
  - Dole for President sticker, 6477.BR0297; Items: 1 (Box 26)
    Candidate: Dole
  - Al Gore for President sticker, 1988; 6477.BR0298; Items: 1 (Box 26)
  - Len Einnehmer Assemblyman sticker, 6477.BR0299; Items: 1 (Box 26)
    Candidate: Einnehmer, Len
  - Dukakis for President sticker, 1988; 6477.BR0300; Items:2 (Box 26)
  - Dick Gephardt for President sticker, 6477.BR0301; Items: 2 (Box 26)
    Candidate: Gephardt, Dick
  - Paul Simon Sticker, 6477.BR0302; Items: 2 (Box 26)
  - Andy O'Rourke for Governor sticker, 6477.BR0303; Items: 1 (Box 26)
    Candidate: O'Rourke, Andy
  - George Bush sticker, 1988; 6477.BR0304; Items: 1 (Box 26)
  - Goodman for Senate sticker, 6477.BR0305; Items: 1 (Box 26)
    Candidate: Goodman
  - Rowland for Governor sticker, 6477.BR0306; Items: 1 (Box 26)
    Candidate: Rowland
  - George and Laura Bush photo, 6477.BR0307; Items: 1 (Box 26)
    Candidate: George W. Bush
  - George Phillips campaign mailings, 6477.BR0308; Items: 4 (Box 26)
    Candidate: George Phillips
    Election: 2012
  - Andrew Cuomo campaign mailings, 6477.BR0309; Items: 4 (Box 26)
    Candidate: Andrew Cuomo
  - Chuck Schumer campaign mailings, 6477.BR0310; Items: 3 (Box 26)
    Candidate: Chuck Schumer
  - Anti-Bush bumper stickers, 6477.BR0311; Items: 2 (Box 28)
    Candidate: Bush, George W.
  - "Take Back the House" bumper sticker, 6477.BR0312; Items: 1 (Box 28)
  - Obama bumper sticker, 6477.BR0313; Items: 1 (Box 28)
- Series V. Buttons
  - Presidents from Washington to McKinley Celluloid Portrait Buttons, ca. 1901; 6477.BT0001; Items: 25 (Box 3)
  - McKinley, Barker and Clark Celluloid Portrait Buttons, ca. 1900-1912; 6477.BT0002; Items: 4 (Box 3)
    Candidate: Barker, Wharton; Clark, James Beauchamp; McKinley, William
    Election: 1900; 1912
    Party: Populist; Democratic; Republican
  - Nixon-Agnew and Watergate Buttons, ca. 1968-1974; 6477.BT0003; Items: 5 (Box 3)
    Election: 1968; 1972
  - Nixon Campaign Buttons, ca. 1960-1972; 6477.BT0004; Items: 5 (Box 4)
  - Ford-Dole Campaign Buttons, ca. 1976; 6477.BT0005; Items: 5 (Box 3)
  - Clinton-Gore Campaign Buttons, ca.1992-1996; 6477.BT0006; Items: 2 (Box 4)
    Candidate: Clinton, William Jefferson
    Election: 1992; 1996
  - Bush 2000 Campaign Button, 2000; 6477.BT0007; Items: 1 (Box 3)
  - Gore-Lieberman Campaign Buttons, ca. 2000; 6477.BT0008; Items: 4 (Box 3)
  - Buckley Senatorial Campaign Button, ca.1968-1980; 6477.BT0009; Items: 2 (Box 4)
  - Humphrey-Muskie Campaign Button, ca. 1968; 6477.BT0010; Items: 1 (Box 4)
  - McGovern-Shriver, Nixon-Agnew and Howard W. Robison Buttons, ca. 1972; 6477.BT0011; Items: 3 (Box 3)
    Candidate: McGovern, George S.; Nixon, Richard M.; Robison, Howard R,
  - Presidential Campaign Buttons, ca. 1884-1968; 6477.BT0012; Items: 13 (Box 3)
    Election: various
  - Romney Campaign Buttons and Tie-Tacks, ca. 1968; 6477.BT0013; Items: 25 (Box 4)
  - Various Campaign Buttons, various; 6477.BT0014; Items: 12 (Box 3)
    Party: various
  - McCarthy Campaign buttons, ca. 1968-1976; 6477.BT0015; Items: 5 (Box 3)
    Election: 1968; 1976
    Party: Independent; New
  - Nixon Campaign Buttons, ca. 1960-1972; 6477.BT0016; Items: 2 (Box 4)
  - Rockefeller Campaign Buttons (Assorted), ca. 1958-1970; 6477.BT0017; Items: 9 (Box 3)
    Election: 1958; 1962; 1964; 1966; 1970
  - Republican National Campaign Items, ca. 1952-1960; 6477.BT0018; Items: 4 (Box 4)
    Election: 1952; 1956; 1960
  - APIC Keynoter Button:"cead mile failte", ca. 1969-1970; 6477.BT0019; Items: 1 (Box 4)
  - Hubert H. Humphrey Button: "HHH", ca. 1968; 6477.BT0020; Items: 1 (Box 4)
  - "I'm For Romney" Button, ca. 1968; 6477.BT0021; Items: 1 (Box 4)
  - "68 Will Open the Gate For Romney" Button, ca. 1968; 6477.BT0022; Items: 1 (Box 4)
  - "Vote Prohibition" Munn-Fisher Campaign Button, 1968; 6477.BT0023; Items: 1 (Box 4)
    Candidate: Munn, E. Harold
    Party: Prohibition
  - "In Your Heart You Know He's Right" Goldwater Campaign Button, ca. 1964; 6477.BT0024; Items: 1 (Box 4)
    Candidate: Goldwater, Barry
  - Goldwater-Miller Campaign Button (Round, gold, with blue letters), ca. 1964; 6477.BT0025; Items: 4 (Box 4)
  - "Wallace for President" Campaign Button, ca. 1964; 6477.BT0026; Items: 1 (Box 4)
    Candidate: Wallace, George C.
  - "Republicans for Johnson" Campaign Button, ca. 1964; 6477.BT0027; Items: 1 (Box 4)
  - "Goldwater for Halloween" L.B.J. Campaign Button, ca. 1964; 6477.BT0028; Items: 1 (Box 4)
  - "Goldwater For President" Photographic Campaign Button, ca. 1984; 6477.BT0029; Items: 1 (Box 4)
  - "Bill Miller" Photographic Campaign Button, ca. 1984; 6477.BT0030; Items: 1 (Box 4)
    Candidate: Miller, William E.
  - "President Nixon. Now More Than Ever" Campaign Button, ca. 1972; 6477.BT0031; Items: 1 (Box 3)
  - "President Nixon. Now More Than Ever" Campaign Button, ca. 1972; 6477.BT0032; Items: 1 (Box 3)
  - "President Nixon. Now More Than Ever" Campaign Button, ca. 1972; 6477.BT0033; Items: 1 (Box 3)
  - "President Nixon. Now More Than Ever" Campaign Button, ca. 1972; 6477.BT0034; Items: 1 (Box 3)
  - "President Nixon. Now More Than Ever" Campaign Button, ca. 1972; 6477.BT0035; Items: 1 (Box 3)